let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "On what island did ancient Greek civilization originate?",
    answer: "Crete",
    options: [
      "Evia",
      "Lesbos",
      "Crete",
      "Rhodes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What were the two most important city states in ancient Greece?",
    answer: "Athens and Sparta",
    options: [
      "Corinth and Thebes",
      "Sparta and Delphi",
      "Thebes and Athens",
      "Athens and Sparta"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the most famous Greek poet?",
    answer: "Homer",
    options: [
      "Sappho",
      "Homer",
      "Hesiod",
      "Pindar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What place is known as the Queen of the Mediterranean Sea?",
    answer: "Greece",
    options: [
      "Greece",
      "Egypt",
      "Italy",
      "Spain"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What did the Greeks call a way of thinking deeply about the world and the meaning of life?",
    answer: "Philosophy",
    options: [
      "Ideology",
      "Ontology",
      "Theory",
      "Philosophy"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Who is the most famous ruler of ancient Athens?",
     answer: "Pericles",
     options: [
       "Cleisthenes",
       "Cimon",
       "Pericles",
       "Leonidas"
     ]
 },

 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "How many years did the Peloponnesian War last?",
  answer: "27 years",
  options: [
    "27 years",
    "5 years",
    "14 years",
    "21 years"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In which civilization did the first Olympic games take place?",
  answer: "Ancient Greece",
  options: [
    "Ancient Rome",
    "Ancient Greece",
    "Ancient Egypt",
    "Ancient Syria"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Where did the Peloponnesian War happen?",
  answer: "Southern Europe",
  options: [
    "Northern Europe",
    "Western Europe",
    "Eastern Europe",
    "Southern Europe"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 10, 
  question: "Who paid for the armor and weapons for the Greek army?",
  answer: "The soldiers bought their own",
  options: [
    "The soldiers bought their own",
    "The city state",
    "Financial elites",
    "The goverment"
  ]
}

];